A Guide to the Population Council records, Accession 1, RG 1 FA210
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 1, 1
  - General File, 1952-1966; 1
    - Grants Authorized
      - United Nations Demographic Training and Research Centre (Bombay) Raja, K.C.K.E., 1956 (Box 15, Folder 235)
      - Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 236)
      - Universita Degli Studi de Perugia (Italy) - Cantalice Project, 1958-1966 (Box 15, Folder 237-238)
      - University of Birmingham (England), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 239)
      - University of California, 1959-1965 (Box 15, Folder 240)
      - University of Cambridge, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 241)
      - University of Chicago - Landau, Richard, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 242)
      - University of Dacca (Pakistan) - Sample Continuing Demographic Survey, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 243)
      - University of Ghana - Friedlander, Dow and Smith, Raymond, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 244)
      - University of Ghana - Olusanya, P. O., 1962 (Box 15, Folder 245)
      - University of Ghana - Research and Teaching in Demography, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 246-247)
      - University of Illinois, 1956-1960 (Box 15, Folder 248)
      - University of Liverpool, 1961-1966 (Box 15, Folder 249)
      - University of Massachusetts, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 250)
      - University of Michigan - Freedman, Ronald, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Folder 251-252)
      - University of Minnesota, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 253)
      - University of Missouri - Hirt, Howard F. (Grant No. 60.09), 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 254)
      - University of Oregon - Heller, Carl, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 255)
      - University of Panjab (Pakistan), 1959-1963 (Box 16, Folder 256)
      - University of Paris - Tuchmann-Duplessis, H., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 257)
      - University of Pennsylvania, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 258)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Kiel Study, 1955-1961 (Box 16, Folder 259-260)
      - University of Pennsylvania Zachariah, K. C., 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 261)
      - University of Philippines Statistical Center, 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 262)
      - University of Puerto Rico, 1953-1957 (Box 16, Folder 263-266)
      - University of San Marcos (Peru), 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 267)
      - University of Sassari (Italy), 1960-1962 (Box 16, Folder 268)
      - University of Southern California - Zinsser, Hans, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 269)
      - University of Uppsala (Sweden), 1956-1961 (Box 16, Folder 270)
      - University of Virginia Shaw, Richard F., 1955-1959 (Box 16, Folder 271-272)
      - University of Washington, 1954-1961 (Box 16, Folder 273-274)
      - Vincent Memorial Hospital, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 275)
      - Washington State University, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 276)
      - Washington University Masters, William H., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 277-278)
      - Wayne State University, 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 279)
      - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology, 1954-1966 (Box 16, Folder 280)
      - Yale University, 1958-1961 (Box 16, Folder 281)
    - H, 1953-1957 (Box 17, Folder 282-283)
    - Harvard, 1953-1958 (Box 17, Folder 284-286)
    - I, 1954-1959 (Box 17, Folder 287-289)
    - India - Grants Authorized A - G, 1953-1960 (Box 17, Folder 290)
    - India - Grants Authorized H - P, 1953-1960 (Box 17, Folder 291)
    - India - Grants Authorized R - Z, 1953-1960 (Box 18, Folder 292-293)
    - Indianapolis Study - Steering Committee, 1941-(1953-1956) (Box 18, Folder 294-296)
    - Indonesia Trip Visit by Dudley Kirk, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 297-298)
    - Industrial College of the Armed Forces, 1953-1958 (Box 18, Folder 299)
    - Institute of Public Health (Japan) Koya, Yoshio, 1953-1956 (Box 18, Folder 300)
    - Institute of Public Health (Japan) Koya, Yoshio, 1956-1959 (Box 19, Folder 301-303)
    - International Congress of Human Genetics (First) Copenhagen, 1954-1956 (Box 19, Folder 304)
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation, 1956-1959 (Box 19, Folder 305-306)
    - International Social Science Council - Grant Authorized - Demographic Seminars, 1953-1956 (Box 19, Folder 307)
    - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population (IUSSP)
      - General Material, 1954-1958 (Box 19, Folder 308)
      - Grant Authorized - General Support, 1952-1958 (Box 19, Folder 309)
      - Grant Authorized - Vienna Conference, 1958-1960 (Box 20, Folder 310)
      - Meeting, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 311-313)
    - Italy, 1954-1958 (Box 20, Folder 314)
    - J, 1954-1959 (Box 20, Folder 315)
    - Japan, 1955-1959 (Box 20, Folder 316-317)
    - John and Mary R. Markle Foundation, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 318)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1955-1958 (Box 20, Folder 319-320)
    - K, 1954-1958 (Box 20, Folder 321-323)
    - Kellogg Foundation, 1955-1957 (Box 21, Folder 324)
    - Krause, John T., 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 325-326)
    - L, 1954-1959 (Box 21, Folder 327-328)
    - M, 1954-1959 (Box 21, Folder 329-332)
    - Medical Schools - Reproduction/Physiology Survey, 1954-1958 (Box 21, Folder 333)
    - Meetings, 1953-1954 (Box 21, Folder 334-335)
    - Miami University (Ohio), 1954-1958 (Box 22, Folder 336)
    - Michigan Study on the Growth of the American Family Freedman, Ronald and Whelpton, Pascal K., 1954-1958 (Box 22, Folder 337-339)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1954-1958 (Box 22, Folder 340-341)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund - Annual Conference, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 342)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund - Annual Conferences, 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 343)
    - Moore, Hugh, 1954-1958 (Box 22, Folder 344)
    - N, 1954-1959 (Box 23, Folder 345-347)
    - National Citizens Committee for the World Health Organization, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 348-349)
    - National Committee on Maternal Health, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 350)
    - National Committee on Maternal Health - Requests for Publications, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 351-352)
    - National Science Foundation, 1956-1959 (Box 23, Folder 353-354)
    - Notestein, Frank - Office of Population Research, 1952-1955 (Box 23, Folder 355-356)
    - O, 1954-1959 (Box 24, Folder 357)
    - P, 1954-1959 (Box 24, Folder 358-359)
    - Pakistan, 1954-1958 (Box 24, Folder 360-361)
    - Pakistan Institute of Development Economics - Seminar on "Problems of Population Growth...", 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 362-363)
    - Personnel - Applications - V, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 364*)
    - Petersen, William, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 365-366)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1953-1956 (Box 24, Folder 367-368)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 369-370)
    - Population Association of America, 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 371-372)
    - Population Association of America - Annual Meetings, 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 373-378)
    - Population Investigation Committee - Glass, David - Grant Authorized, 1955-1958 (Box 25, Folder 379-380)
    - Population Reference Bureau, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 381)
    - Population Reference Bureau - Cook, Robert C., 1953-1955 (Box 25, Folder 382-383)
    - Population Reference Bureau - Cook, Robert C., 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 384-385)
    - Preparation of Training Materials in Population, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 386)
    - Princeton University, 1952-1958 (Box 26, Folder 387)
    - Princeton University - Coale-Hoover Report on Economic Development, 1956-1959 (Box 26, Folder 388)
    - Princeton University - Conference on the Interrelations of Demographic and Economic Change, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 389)
    - R, 1954-1961 (Box 26, Folder 390-391)
    - Reece Committee, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 392)
    - Research Group for European Migration Problems (REMP), 1952-1959 (Box 26, Folder 393-394)
    - Research Group for European Migration Problems (REMP), 1954-1957 (Box 27, Folder 395)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Allen, Yorke, 1954-1958 (Box 27, Folder 396-397)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Grants to Population Council, 1955-1966 (Box 27, Folder 398)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Special Studies Project, 1956-1958 (Box 27, Folder 399)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - General Correspondence, 1951-1958 (Box 27, Folder 400-402)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - Grants to the Population Council, 1961-1967 (Box 27, Folder 403-404)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - New Delhi, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 405-406)
    - Rockefeller Foundation - New York - Balfour, M. C., 1958 (Box 27, Folder 407-408)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Tarrytown Meeting, 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 409)
    - S, 1953-1959 (Box 28, Folder 410-412)
    - Staff (Box 28)
      - Balfour, M. C.- Memoranda and Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 413-414)
      - Balfour, M. C.-Tour Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 415-416)
      - Berelson, Bernard - Administration, 1961-1965 (Box 28, Folder 417-419)
      - Berelson, Bernard - Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 420-423)
      - Berelson, Bernard - Administration - Memoranda, 1962-1966 (Box 29, Folder 424-425)
      - Berelson, Bernard - Speeches and Articles, 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 426-427)
      - Berelson, Bernard - Travel - India, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 428-429)
      - Berelson, Bernard - Travel - Latin America, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 430-431)
      - Berelson, Bernard - Travel - Taiwan, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 432-433)
      - Berelson, Bernard - Travel - Turkey, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 434)
      - Fisher, Raymond G., 1953-1955 (Box 30, Folder 435)
      - Kirk, Dudley, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 436-437)
      - Kirk, Dudley - Demographic Advisory Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 30, Folder 438)
      - Kirk, Dudley - Demographic Advisory Committee - Meeting Agendas, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 439)
      - Kirk, Dudley - Demographic Advisory Committee - Meeting Summaries, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 440)
      - Kirk, Dudley - Demographic Projects - Budgets, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 441)
      - Kirk, Dudley - Memoranda, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 442-443)
      - Mauldin, Parker Trips, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 444-445)
      - Nelson, Warren O., 1953-1955 (Box 30, Folder 446-448)
      - Notestein, Frank, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 449)
      - Notestein, Frank, 1963-1966 (Box 31, Folder 450-454)
      - Notestein, Frank - Requests for Speeches and Articles, 1959-1966 (Box 31, Folder 455-457)
      - Notestein, Frank - Travel, 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 458)
      - Notestein, Frank W. Travel, 1959-1966 (Box 32, Folder 459-462)
      - Staff Osborn, Frederick, 1953 1955 (Box 32, Folder 463-464)
      - Osborn, Frederick - Memoranda, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 465)
      - Robbin, Jonathan, 1955-1958 (Box 32, Folder 466-467)
      - Stouffer, Samuel A., 1959-1961 (Box 32, Folder 468-469)
      - Whelpton, Pascal K., 1954 (Box 32, Folder 470)
    - Staff Meetings, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 471-472)
    - T, 1953-1959 (Box 32, Folder 473)
    - Taeuber, Irene, 1954-1958 (Box 33, Folder 474-475)
    - Taiwan, 1955-1959 (Box 33, Folder 476-477)
    - Teaching of Demography
      - Eldridge Bibliography, 1955-1958 (Box 33, Folder 478-479)
      - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population (IUSSP), 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 480)
      - Stockholm Meeting, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 481)
      - United Nations Educational, Social and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) Study - International Survey, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 482-484)
      - United States Study, 1951-1956 (Box 34, Folder 485-486)
    - Trustees, Board of
      - General Material, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 487-488)
      - Committee on Program and Succession (Haskins Committee), 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 489)
      - Executive Committee, 1960-1966 (Box 34, Folder 490-491)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 1966 December 21 (Box 34, Folder 492)
      - Finance Committee, 1957-1965 (Box 34, Folder 493)
      - Meetings, 1956 October 30 (Box 34, Folder 494)
      - Meetings, 1957 January 10 (Box 34, Folder 495)
      - Meetings, 1957 April 5 (Box 34, Folder 496)
      - Meetings, 1957 October 3 (Box 34, Folder 497)
      - Meetings, 1958 January 16 (Box 35, Folder 498)
      - Meetings, 1958 May 16 (Box 35, Folder 499-500)
      - Meetings, 1958 November 13 (Box 35, Folder 501)
      - Meetings, 1959 January 21 (Box 35, Folder 502)
      - Meetings, 1959 May 13 (Box 35, Folder 503)
      - Meetings, 1959 October 14 (Box 35, Folder 504)
      - Meetings, 1960 January 6 (Box 35, Folder 505)
      - Meetings, 1960 April 5 (Box 35, Folder 506)
      - Meetings, 1960 October 19 (Box 35, Folder 507)
      - Meetings, 1961 January 11 (Box 36, Folder 508)
      - Meetings, 1961 May 8 (Box 36, Folder 509)
      - Meetings, 1961 October 25 (Box 36, Folder 510)
      - Meetings, 1961 December 20 (Box 36, Folder 511)
      - Meetings, 1962 March 14 (Box 36, Folder 512)
      - Meetings, 1962 May 23 (Box 36, Folder 513)
      - Meetings, 1962 October 10 (Box 36, Folder 514)
      - Meetings, 1963 January 7 (Box 36, Folder 515)
      - Meetings, 1963 April 17 (Box 36, Folder 516)
      - Meetings, 1963 October 9 (Box 36, Folder 517)
      - Meetings, 1964 January 14 (Box 36, Folder 518)
      - Meetings, 1964 May 20 (Box 36, Folder 519)
      - Meetings, 1964 October 14 (Box 36, Folder 520)
      - Meetings, 1965 January 13 (Box 36, Folder 521)
      - Meetings, 1965 April 21 (Box 36, Folder 522)
      - Meetings, 1965 October 20 (Box 36, Folder 523)
      - Meetings, 1965 December 15 (Box 36, Folder 524)
      - Meetings, 1966 April 20 (Box 36, Folder 525)
      - Meetings, 1966 October 19 (Box 36, Folder 526)
      - Members - Black, Eugene, 1960-1964 (Box 36, Folder 527)
      - Members - Boudreau, Frank, 1953-1965 (Box 36, Folder 528)
      - Members - Bronk, Detlev W., 1952-1966 (Box 37, Folder 529)
      - Members - Bunker, Ellsworth, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 530)
      - Members - Bunting, Mary I., 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 531)
      - Members - Compton, Karl T., 1952-1954 (Box 37, Folder 532-533)
      - Members - Conant, James B., 1957-1963 (Box 37, Folder 534)
      - Members - Ebert, Robert H., 1966 (Box 37, Folder 535)
      - Members - Haskins, Caryl, 1956-1964 (Box 37, Folder 536)
      - Members - McLean, Donald, 1951-1965 (Box 37, Folder 537-539)
      - Members - Notestein, Frank W., 1956-1959 (Box 37, Folder 540)
      - Members - Notestein, Frank W.-Travel, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 541-543)
      - Members - Osborn, Frederick, 1956-1962 (Box 38, Folder 544)
      - Members - Parran, Thomas, 1953-1966 (Box 38, Folder 545)
      - Members - Reston, James, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 546)
      - Members - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd, 1952-1966 (Box 38, Folder 547-553)
      - Members - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Donations, 1959-1966 (Box 39, Folder 554)
      - Members - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Travel - Asia, 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 555)
      - Members - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Travel - Latin America, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 556)
      - Members - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Travel - Middle East, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 557-558)
      - Members - Scanlon, John J., 1962-1964 (Box 39, Folder 559)
      - Members - Schultz, Theodore W., 1956-1966 (Box 39, Folder 560)
      - Members - Strauss, Lewis, 1953-1966 (Box 39, Folder 561)
      - Members - White, Gilbert F., 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 562)
      - Twin Study, 1952-1956 (Box 39, Folder 563-567)
      - Twin Study, 1957-1958 (Box 40, Folder 568)
      - Twin Study-Firsche in Twin Report, 1954-1956 (Box 40, Folder 569)
    - U, 1953-1959 (Box 40, Folder 570-571)
    - United Arab Republic, 1956-1957 (Box 40, Folder 572)
    - United Nations, 1953-1958 (Box 40, Folder 573-575)
    - United Nations - Kirk, Dudley, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 576)
    - United Nations Demographic Training and Research Centre
      - Bombay, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 577)
      - Bombay - Bright, Margaret, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 578)
      - Bombay - Grants, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 579)
      - Bombay - Raja, K.C.K.E., 1957-1959 (Box 40, Folder 580)
      - Bombay - Raja, K.C.K.E.-School Children Study, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 581)
      - Grants, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 582)
      - Santiago, 1954-1959 (Box 41, Folder 583-584)
      - Santiago - Junta Asesora, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 585)
      - Shryock, Henry, 1957-1958 (Box 41, Folder 586)
      - Thomas, Dorothy, 1957-1958 (Box 41, Folder 587-588)
    - United States
      - Bureau of the Census, 1954-1958 (Box 41, Folder 589)
      - Department of Agriculture, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 590)
      - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1953-1958 (Box 41, Folder 591)
      - Department of State, 1954-1955 (Box 41, Folder 592)
    - University of California, 1954-1955 (Box 41, Folder 593)
    - University of Chicago, 1955-1957 (Box 41, Folder 594)
    - University of Chicago Grant Application, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 595)
    - University of Connecticut, 1954-1955 (Box 42, Folder 596)
    - University of London, 1956-1958 (Box 42, Folder 597)
    - University of Michigan, 1953-1955 (Box 42, Folder 598)
    - University of Missouri, 1956-1958 (Box 42, Folder 599)
    - University of New Mexico, 1955-1958 (Box 42, Folder 600)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1957-1958 (Box 42, Folder 601-602)
    - University of Pennsylvania Schwab, William Discretionary Grant, 1955-1959 (Box 42, Folder 603)
    - University of Puerto Rico, 1954-1960 (Box 42, Folder 604-605)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1956-1959 (Box 42, Folder 606)
    - V, 1954-1959 (Box 42, Folder 607)
    - W, 1953-1959 (Box 42, Folder 608)
    - W, 1953-1959 (Box 43, Folder 609-611)
    - Whitney, Vincent H., 1957-1959 (Box 43, Folder 612)
    - Whitney, Vincent H. Memoranda, 1957-1958 (Box 43, Folder 613-614)
    - World Population Conference
      - General Material, 1952-1955 (Box 43, Folder 615)
      - General Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 43, Folder 616-617)
      - Conferees' Forms, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 618)
      - Miscellany, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 619)
      - Participants, 1954-1955 (Box 44, Folder 620-621)
      - Printed Material, 1952-1953 (Box 44, Folder 622)
      - Session # 23 - Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 44, Folder 623)
      - Session # 23 - Summaries, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 624-625)
      - Session # 25, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 626)
      - United Nations Memoranda, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 627)
    - Y, 1954-1959 (Box 44, Folder 628-629)
    - Z, 1956-1958 (Box 44, Folder 630)
  - Grant Files, 1958-1966; 2
    Correspondence and memoranda relating to grant applications and the administering of funds. They also include letters and reports which summarize studies undertaken with grant support. Many grant files are very brief, and for some grants only the grant authorization or the letter of award may be available. Almost always researchers have applied for and received grants through the institutions with which they were affiliated. The institutions administered the grants for the benefit of the individual researcher(s) undertaking the study described in the grant proposal.
    Grant Files are arranged by number with the exception of a few unnumbered grants which are filed by year at the front of the file. Grant numbers have two parts, separated by a decimal point. The digits to the left of the decimal point designate the year in which a grant was made. The digits to the right of the decimal point designate the order in which grants were awarded during a given year. A letter M, D, or T, indicates whether the grant was made under the aegis of the Biomedical Division, the Demographic Division, or the Technical Assistance Division, respectively.
    For example, M65.34 - signifies the thirty-fourth grant of 1965. The letter M indicates that the grant was for biomedical research. For a single year, there is one series of grant numbers in which medical, demographic, and technical grants are included. For example, M65.34 - would be followed by a grant numbered 65.35. That grant could be either a medical, demographic, or technical grant.
    Former Classification: IV 3B 04.3a
    Indexing to the Grant Files is provided by FA775 Population Council records, Index, Series 2: Central File Index, 1961-1976.
    - University of Washington: Fellowships, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 631)
    - Mt. Sinai Hospital, NY: Research in Conception Control, 1958-1961 (Box 45, Folder 632)
    - United Nations: DTRC Expenses, 1959-1964 (Box 45, Folder 633-634)
    - Bar Harbor Courses in Medical Genetics: Participants' Expenses, 1960-1963 (Box 45, Folder 635)
    - Grant # D59.32 - University of Bombay: Demographic Program (Box 45, Folder 636-639)
    - Grant # D60.4 - University College of Ghana: Demography Course (Box 45, Folder 640)
    - Grant # D60.29 - Johns Hopkins University: Cooperative Project in Demography (Box 45, Folder 641)
    - Grant # D61.14 - Central Statistical Office, Pakistan: Population Growth Study (Box 45, Folder 642-643)
    - Grant # D61.18 - University of California, Berkeley: Public Health Education Research Project at Dacca, East Pakistan (Box 45, Folder 644)
    - Grant # D61.19 - Johns Hopkins University: Cooperative Project in Demography (Box 45, Folder 645)
    - Grant # D61.20 - University of Ghana: Demographic Program (Box 46, Folder 646-648)
    - Grant # D61.25 - University of Chicago: Population Research and Training Center (Box 46, Folder 649)
    - Grant # M61.39 - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology: Reproductive Biology (Box 46, Folder 650)
    - Grant # M61.61 - Tohoku University, Japan: Equipment Purchase (Box 46, Folder 651)
    - Grant # D62.4 - University of Chicago: Research Program (Box 46, Folder 652-653)
    - Grant # D62.5 - University of the West Indies: Census Research Program (Box 46, Folder 654)
    - Grant # D62.7 - Nippon Medical School, Japan: Family Planning Studies (Box 46, Folder 655)
    - Grant # D62.8 - Selected Universities (U.S.): Support of Publications (Box 46, Folder 656)
    - Grant # D62.9 - University of British Columbia: Antifertility Substances Studies (Box 46, Folder 657)
    - Grant # D62.10 - University of California, Davis: Ovarian Function Studies (Box 46, Folder 658)
    - Grant # M62.11 - College de France: Ovulation Control Studies (Box 46, Folder 659)
    - Grant # M62.12 - Research Laboratory, Denmark: Role of Connective Tissue in Reproduction (Box 46, Folder 660)
    - Grant # M62.13 - Maudsley Hospital, Eng.: Neural Control Studies (Box 46, Folder 661)
    - Grant # M62.14 - Seton Hall College of Medicine, N.J.: Visit of Cyril Clark, M.D. (Box 47, Folder 662)
    - Grant # M62.15 - Nagasaki University, School of Medicine: Potential Anti-Progestins Studies (Box 47, Folder 663)
    - Grant # M62.16 - New England Center Hospital: Estrogen Studies (Box 47, Folder 664)
    - Grant # M62.17 - Research Foundation of SUNY: Chemical Morphology Spermatozoa Studies (Box 47, Folder 665)
    - Grant # M62.18 - Washington State University: Tubo - Ovarian Mechanisms Studies (Box 47, Folder 666)
    - Grant # D62.20 - U.N. - CELADE, Chile: General Purposes (Box 47, Folder 667-668)
    - Grant # D62.21 - University of Michigan: Field Studies in Taiwan (JCRR) (Box 47, Folder 669)
    - Grant # D62.22 - Yonsei University, Korea: Family Planning Research (Box 47, Folder 670)
    - Grant # D62.23 - Jadavpur University, India: Immigration in West Bengal (Box 47, Folder 671)
    - Grant # M62.24 - Boston University: Metabolic Properties of Eggs and Ovarian Secretions (Box 47, Folder 672)
    - Grant # M62.25 - IUCD Conference, NY: Financing (Box 47, Folder 673-674)
    - Grant # M62.26 - Chelsea Hospital for Women, Eng.: Cervical Mucus and Vaginal Cytology in Fertility (Box 47, Folder 675)
    - Grant # M26.27 - Guy's Hospital Medical School, Eng.: Effects of Drugs on Pregnancy (Box 47, Folder 676)
    - Grant # M62.28 - Hebrew University, Israel: Influence of Steroids on Ovarian and Adrenal Function (Box 47, Folder 677)
    - Grant # M62.29 - University of Montreal: Stress and Fertility (Box 47, Folder 678)